

GUIDO VAN DIJK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

WHO AM I?

My name is Guido van Dijk, 24 years old, and born in The Netherlands.

I am a Front-end developer with 5 and a half years of design and web development experience.
I specialize in Vue.js and JavaScript ES-Next, which I use to create optimized, accessible websites and applications, in a short amount of time.

My main objective is to grow as a developer, working with all kinds of techniques to expand my knowledge about developing websites and applications as both front- and backend.

SKILL SET

JavaScript, Vue.js, React (Native), TypeScript, C#, Java, Kotlin, Swift, PHP, MySQL, NoSQL, (S)CSS, HTML, Scrum, Git, Agile, Bitbucket, Atlassian, Jira, Photoshop, Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD,

INFORMATION

- van.quido@hotmail.com
- GitHub
- <u>LinkedIn</u>

EXPERIENCE

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER • YUMMYGUM • FEBRUARI 2023 – JULY 2023

I set up a React Native component library with Expo, Storybook and other functionality to ensure applications that will be build with this library adhere to accessibility and code quality requirements of Yummygum. I have also worked on a client project "Classroomscreen", where I have developed the front-end of the website in Vue.js.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER • THE VALLEY • JULY 2018 – JULY 2022

I developed campaign websites for Postcode-, Vrienden-, and BuurtLoterij. I helped expand the front-end of our sales platform Nominow with Vue.js. And developed client websites for Nike, Tommy Hilfiger, and their daughter companies with frameworks that work best for their use-cases, products, and specifications.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER / UI DESIGNER • FBI DESIGN • SEP 2017 – JUNE 2018

I designed and developed WordPress websites for a wide array of clients, large and small located in and around Haarlem.

FREELANCE UX/UI DESIGNER • NEXTAIL • DEC 2016 – JAN 2017

I was responsible for setting up the campaigns and creating content for the social media accounts of the Blokker holding (Bart Smit, Leenbakker, Intertoys, and Cook&Co). I designed promotional products for the 70th birthday of De Huishouds Beurs and created a design for the new website of Intertoys.

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY • 2023 • HOGESCHOOL INHOLLAND HAARLEM

DESIGN FOR INTERACTION • 2019 • MEDIA COLLEGE AMSTERDAM